Yu,
Ms. Liang said
she's quite satisfied with you.
You did well this time.
I had someone pick a date.
The first of next month is a good day.
You two
will get engaged then.
I don't agree to this marriage.
Why?
I don't like Ms. Liang.
Does it matter if you like her?
Your brother
chose Shu Roujing out of love back then.
Look at
what their marriage has become now.
Exactly.
Don't follow
in your brother's footsteps.
I'm fine.
My foot is just a bit itchy.
Sir,
I actually think
Miss Liang is quite suitable
to be our second daughter-in-law.
I liked her very much
the first time I saw her.
Isn't that right, Mei?
Ms. Liang is indeed a nice person.
Then it's settled.
Let's eat.
Zhangxin,
don't worry.
I won't agree to this marriage.
If you marry into the Liang family,
you'll have the Liang Group backing you.
This way, your chances against He Shi
will be better.
Is my marriage
just a part of your revenge to you?
That's not what I meant.
I just wanted you
to have a higher status in the He family.
But I'd rather
my feelings be pure.
Second Brother,
I like you.
You're crazy.
We're siblings.
Don't you
have any romantic feelings for me at all?
I don't want
to think about this right now.
I just want to get rid of
Zhang Xin and He Shi.
I will help you,
and I will wait for you.
But before that,
please don't
push me to other women,
okay?
Master,
You're still awake?
I actually know
the real reason why Xiaoyu
refuses to marry.
I just
saw him and Li Zhangxin...
This is outrageous!
Tell me,
if a guy
hasn't texted for three days,
does it mean he doesn't like me?
Of course
not.
How could any man not like
a woman as beautiful as Miss Liang?
Right?
He must be feeling insecure,
afraid he's not good enough for you.
The food
is getting cold.
Let's go eat.
Yeah,
let's eat.
I know everything
about you two.
Let's just leave it at that for now.
I truly love Li Zhangxin.
Nonsense!
Do you want the outside world to know
that neither you nor He Shi
are my biological children?
I'll find a good time
to announce this.
Don't worry.
I absolutely won't let
the He Group's stock price
be affected.
There's no way
I'm letting you take this risk.
But we can't
let Second Brother's marriage
become a tool to win over the Liang Group.
Everything he has today,
I gave to him.
The He family has raised him
for so many years.
It's time he learned to repay the favor.
If it isn't Ms. Liang.
Coming to my house every other day,
are you that eager
to marry my brother?
You are
He Shi.
Where is He Yu?
Do you know why He Yu
doesn't want to marry you?
He feels inferior
and thinks he's not good enough for me.
There's something wrong with his head.
You're not
his type at all.
Then what is his type?
He likes
Li Zhangxin.
Aren't
they...
aren't they siblings?
That's why I said
there's something wrong with his head.
He won't even spare his own sister.
Why don't you consider me?
Other than being married,
I have no flaws.
You...
You're so amazing, sir!
Ms. Liang,
if there's anything lacking
in our hospitality,
please let us know.
Sir,
I like the He family.
Okay.
You try.
But I don't really know how to play.
How about
letting He Yu teach me?
Sorry, Ms. Liang.
I don't know how either.
I'll teach you.
Can you do it?
Seriously.
Go sit over there.
Like this.
Can I teach you now?
I'll do it myself.
I said I'll teach you.
Hold the cue like this.
Ms. Liang,
you must know a lot
about the He family.
It is just as you think.
You are not suitable for the He family.
Nor are you suitable
for the Second Young Master.
I hope you stay out of this.
Otherwise,
I don't know
what offensive things I might do to you.
This is the first time someone has dared
to speak to me like this.
Li Zhangxin,
you think too highly of yourself.
I don't want to make an enemy out of you.
He Yu likes you.
That already makes us enemies.
Then don't blame me.
didn't remind you.
Yes.
This is a handmade vase
my second brother gave me.
Don't break it.
This is a handmade vase
I bought in Denmark.
It's a global limited edition,
the only one.
This isn't her.
Ms. Liang
is being too blatant in trying to harm me.
My dad finally got me back,
and you almost made him lose me again.
Are you okay?
Liang Chunsheng,
if anything happens to Zhangxin...
I won't let you get away with this.
So it was the maid
who put the vase in the wrong place
and got in Miss Liang's way.
As long as you're okay.
Clean this up.
It's just a vase.
It's not worth much.
Someone,
come and clean this up.
Sir,
I really didn't mean it.
It's okay.
Are you alright?
Okay.
What are you thinking about?
Don't you think
Dad doesn't love us at all?
He is the head of the family, after all.
What happened today
might be because he's
afraid of offending the Liang Group.
I just feel like
he doesn't care about anyone.
He lets Zhang Xin bully me, Mom,
and Shu Roujing.
He even treats your marriage
as a bargaining chip.
Don't think like that.
If Dad didn't love you,
why would he go through so much trouble
to find you?
He almost got scammed.
Zhangxin,
Dad and I are both so happy
you're back.
Sis,
forget about those jerks.
Exactly.